**Privacy Notice**

**Last modified March 2020**

This Privacy Notice will help you understand what personal information FEDERATION INTERNATIONALE DE HOCKEY, Nagravision SA, its ultimate parent company Kudelski S.A. and its affiliates (collectively the Kudelski Group) collect and use when providing Services to you and your privacy rights associated with that personal information.

For the purposes of this Privacy Notice, "Services" refers to marketing, promotional, and customer relationship management and other activities carried out on behalf of FEDERATION INTERNATIONALE DE HOCKEY by Nagravision SA.

Unless expressly specified herein, it does not include personal information collected by other products and solutions commercialized by the Kudelski Group, which are governed by privacy terms made available with such specific products and solutions.

**Contact � Privacy Committee**

Nagravision SA is an affiliate of Kudelski SA and part of the Kudelski Group, headquartered in Cheseaux-sur-Lausanne, Switzerland with American headquarters in Phoenix, Arizona, United States of America. The Kudelski Group has appointed a Privacy Committee to contact if you have any question or concerns about personal data handling policies and practices. Please send your inquiry to [**privacy@nagra.com**](mailto:privacy@nagra.com). In your email, please describe in as much detail as possible the nature of your inquiry or the ways in which you believe that the Privacy Notice has not been complied with.

**Changes and updates to the Privacy Notice**

As our Services to you may change from time to time, this Privacy Notice may need to be updated accordingly. Nagravision SA reserves the right to amend this Privacy Notice at any time at its sole discretion and will provide notice of material changes on this website. We may email you (provided you have an email address registered with us) about material changes therein, prior to them becoming effective but we invite you to consult this page on a regular basis to get information on our latest privacy practices. By continuing to use the Services after changes to the Privacy Notice have become effective, you are giving your agreement to the revised Notice with the following exception: if at the time you provide personal information to Nagravision SA or to one of its affiliates you are given the opportunity to limit how such information will be used to communicate with you, either by Nagravision SA, by one of its affiliates or by third parties, Nagravision SA will not change your preference in this regard without your express consent. However, if Nagravision SA sells assets (or the assets of a division or subsidiary) to another entity, or Nagravision SA (or a division or subsidiary) is acquired by, or merged with, another entity, Nagravision SA may provide to such entity customer information that is related to that part of our business that was sold to, or merged with, the other entity without your consent.

If, as the result of such changes, you want to alter the ways in which Nagravision SA is allowed to use your personal information, you can do so by following the procedure described below in the section titled �Access and Control over your Personal Information�.

**Children�s privacy**

We do not knowingly collect personal information from individuals under age 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any personal information through the Services. If you have reason to believe that we may have accidentally received personal information from an individual under age 13, please contact us immediately at [privacy@nagra.com](mailto:privacy@nagra.com).

If you are visiting, residing in or resident of the Europe Economic Area, and under the age of 16, then you must obtain your parent�s or legal guardian�s permission to consent to the collection and processing of your personal data.

**Personal information we collect and use**

Nagravision SA collects personal information (also referenced as personal data) about its customers and other individuals for the purpose of providing the Services to them. The personal information collected falls into several categories described below. A detailed list (or categories) of personal information and its purpose is provided at the end of this document.

1\. Customer Relationship Management

We may ask for certain information, such as your first name and last name, gender, postal address, telephone number, email address, proof of identity (passport number, identification card number, etc) and other information, from you in order to provide the Services to you, or if you contact or interact with us. We may also retain any messages you send through the Services and may retain other information you voluntarily provide us with, including but not limited to your comments and other content. We use this information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the Services, and as further detailed below.

2\. Information we may collect and/or receive from third parties

We may receive information about you from third parties including third party social networking services. You should always review, and if necessary, adjust your privacy settings on third party websites and services before linking or connecting them to the Services. We also may collect information about you from third party business partners, publicly available sources and our subsidiaries and affiliates.

In order to reduce errors in our database, authenticate our users and prevent abuse of our system, we may on occasion supplement the personal information you submit to us with information from third-party sources. For example, we may supplement your registration information with address information provided by the relevant in-country postal service to qualify your information and prevent errors in our database.

3\. Commercial and marketing communications

We use the information we collect or receive to communicate directly with you. We may send you electronic messages containing Service-related notices (e.g., account verification, purchase and billing confirmations and reminders, feature notifications, technical and security notices). We may also send you electronic messages containing product and/or service offerings, promotions, invitations and special offers. You can also stop receiving electronic messages (other than Service-related notices) from us by clicking on the "unsubscribe link" provided in such communications or by changing your account preferences or settings.

4\. Analytics information

We may directly collect information, or we or our third party business partners may use analytics tools to help us measure traffic and usage trends for the Services (�Analytics Information�).

5\. Cookies and website tracking

Our Services uses cookies and other technologies to provide enhanced functionality on the site, track data traffic and aggregate traffic movement (e.g. what pages are popular, what sequence of webpages are visited) for analysis, , website optimization and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

These technologies record information about your use of our websites, including:

� Browser and device data, such as IP address, region or general location where your computer or device is accessing the internet, device type, operating system and Internet browser type, screen resolution, operating system name and version, device manufacturer and model, language, plug-ins, add-ons and the language version of the sites you are visiting.

� Usage data, such as time spent on the sites, pages visited, links clicked, language preferences, and the pages that led or referred you to our sites.

To learn more about the cookies that may be served through our websites and how you can control our use of cookies and third-party analytics, please see below.

5.1 Information on cookie use

A cookie is a small text file placed on your computer, to help us analyze how you use our websites. When you visit the website again, the cookie enables the website to recognize your browser and deliver an improved user experience (saving time or retrieving pieces of information for a customized experience).

We use first-party cookies (set by us) and third-party cookies (set by our marketing and analytics partners) that enable features such as advertising, interactive content and analytics to be provided.

The types of cookies we use are:

� **Essential website cookies**: These cookies are strictly necessary to provide you with services available through our websites, subscription services and mobile apps and to use some of its features, such as access to secure areas.

� **Analytics and customization cookies**: These cookies collect information that is used either in aggregate form to help us understand how our website and subscription services are being used or how effective our email campaigns are, or to help us customize our website for you.

� **Performance and functionality cookies**: These cookies are used to enhance the performance and functionality of our website, subscription service and mobile apps but are non-essential to their use. However, without these cookies, certain functionality may become unavailable.

In particular, our website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (�Google�) that uses cookies. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the websites (including your anonymized IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however, please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of the website. By using the Services, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.

5.2 How you can control cookies

You can typically remove or reject cookies via your browser settings. In order to do this, follow the instructions provided by your browser (usually located within the �settings,� �help� �tools� or �edit� facility). Many browsers are set to accept cookies until you change your settings.

Further information about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set on your computer or mobile device and how to manage and delete them, visit [**www.youronlinechoices.com**](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/)

If you do not accept our cookies, you may experience some inconvenience in your use of our website. For example, we may not be able to recognize your computer or mobile device and you may need to log in every time you visit our website.

6\. Google advertising

Our Services use Google advertising for remarketing purpose, which will display advertising for people who have previously visited our websites or used our applications. For that purpose, our Services will collect information such as your IP address and device identifier. It will NOT use personally identifiable information such as your name, address, email address or telephone number. You can opt out of Google's use of cookies or device identifiers by visiting Google's Ads Settings ( http://www.google.com/settings/ads). Alternatively, opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising initiative opt-out page ([http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt\_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)) or control the use of device identifiers by using your [device�s settings](https://support.google.com/ads/answer/1660762#mob).

7\. Log file information

Log file information is automatically reported by your browser each time you access a web page or other content within the Services. We may also receive log information relating to your device and your use of our Apps. When you use the Services, our servers automatically record certain log file information (�Server Logs�). These Server Logs may include anonymous information such as your web request, Internet Protocol (IP) address, operating system, browser type, referring/exit pages and URLs, number of clicks and how you interact with links on the Service, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed, and other such information. The information contained in Server Logs is used to monitor, assess, manage, diagnose problems with, improve and otherwise administer the Services.

8\. Device identifiers

When you access the Services by or through a mobile device (including but not limited to smart phones or tablets), we and/or our third party business partners may access, assign, collect, monitor and/or remotely store one or more unique device-specific identifiers, such as a universally unique identifier (UUID) (�Unique Identifiers�). Unique Identifiers are small data files or similar data structures stored on and/or associated with your mobile device, which uniquely identify your mobile device. A Unique Identifier may be data stored in connection with the device hardware, data stored in connection with the device's operating system or other software, or data sent to the device by us. A Unique Identifier may convey information to us about how you browse and use the Service. A Unique Identifier may also be used to help you log in faster and enhance your navigation through the Service.

9\. Location data

When you access the Service by or through a mobile device, we may access, collect, monitor and/or remotely store location data, which may include GPS coordinates (e.g. latitude and/or longitude) or similar information regarding the location of your mobile device (�Location Data�). Location Data may convey to us information about how you browse and use the Service. Location Data may be used to personalize and customize your experience when using the Service, facilitate the functionality of certain features within the Service, and to improve the Service. Some features of the Service, particularly location-based services, may not function properly if use or availability of Location Data is impaired or disabled. Your device configuration settings allow you to disable location tracking. Please refer to the instructions for your mobile device�s operating system.

**Do Not Track signals**

Some internet browsers may be configured to send �Do Not Track� signals to the online services that you visit. We currently respect any do not track signals. To find out more about �Do Not Track,� please visit [**http://www.allaboutdnt.com**](http://www.allaboutdnt.com/).

**Third party websites**

Please note that Nagravision SA is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of non-Nagravision SA websites to which the website may link. You should review the privacy notice of such websites before using the sites.

**Sharing of your personal information with third parties**

Nagravision SA may share your information with third party business partners for which we are providing Services. Examples include but are not limited to Sports Leagues and Sports Federation.  
Nagravision SA may share information with third party business partners that function on our behalf. Examples include, but are not limited to, companies that assist us with serving advertisement within the Services, analyzing data, and providing marketing assistance. We may share information about you that they need to perform their functions. We will use contractual or other means to protect personal information disclosed to such third parties. We may also share your information with any subsidiary or affiliate of ours for purposes consistent with this Privacy Notice. Any subsidiary or affiliate of ours will be required to maintain that information in accordance with this Privacy Notice.  
We may also disclose your personal information to any third party with your prior consent.

**Legal basis for processing personal information**

The legal basis for the processing of your personal Information as described above is your consent or our need for processing your personal information in order to be able to deliver the Services or to provide you with the requested information. You have the right to withdraw consent at any time, without affecting the lawfulness of processing based on consent before its withdrawal.

**International transfer of personal information**

1.  Within the Kudelski Group: When you submit personal information to Nagravision SA or one of its affiliates through a website or other digital and print means, you understand and agree that this information may be transferred across national boundaries and may be stored and processed by Nagravision SA and its affiliates in any of the countries in which the Kudelski Group maintains offices, including without limitation, the European Economic Area, Switzerland, and the USA.  We put in place appropriate contractual data protection agreements or use other appropriate legal mechanisms to safeguard the transfer of information.
2.  Transfers to third parties: You also acknowledge that in certain countries or with respect to certain activities, the collection, transferring, storage and processing of your information may be undertaken by technology vendor partners working with us (see above).

**Security of your personal information**

Nagravision SA and its affiliates have put in place appropriate physical, technical measures and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent your personal information from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. We update and test such security measures on an ongoing basis and restrict access to your personal information to those employees who need to know that information to provide Services to you. Our employees receive training about privacy matters, including confidentiality and security of your personal information.

**Retention of your personal information**

Our policy is to retain your data for a reasonable period of time, taking into consideration our need to provide information that you have requested on company, service and product development and comply with legal requirements.

We retain information from cookies and other tracking technologies for a reasonable period of time from the date the information was created.

**Access and control over your personal information**

Nagravision SA makes it possible for you to access your personal Information and more particularly to:

*   review, correct, update or delete the personal information you have supplied us with, to the extent that is not otherwise permitted or required to keep such data for continuing providing the Services;
*   object to certain data processing operations or ask us to restrict processing of your personal information;
*   opt-out of the sale of personal information to third parties;
*   receive a copy of the personal information the business has shared with third parties and the names and addresses of the third parties with whom the business has shared such information (for residents of California, USA, such information shared during the immediately preceding calendar year);
*   if we have collected and processed your personal information based on your consent, withdraw such consent at any time; or
*   receive a copy of your personal information processed by us.

To exercise any of those rights, you may unsubscribe at any given time using the link provided in the email or contact us directly at [**privacy@nagra.com**](mailto:privacy@nagra.com) or by mail to:

Nagravision SA

PO Box 134  
Route de Gen�ve 22-24  
1033 Cheseaux-sur-Lausanne

Switzerland

Attn. Privacy Committee

**Changes to our Privacy Notice**

We may update or modify this Privacy Notice at any time and from time to time without prior notice. Please review this Privacy Notice periodically, and especially before you provide any information. This Privacy Notice was made effective on the date indicated at the beginning of this document.

**Supervisory authority**

If you reside within the European Economic Area and if you wish to raise a concern about our use of your information (and without prejudice to any other rights you may have), you have the right to do so with your local supervisory authority. You can find your supervisory authority by visiting [https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members\_en](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en)

**Categories of personal data and purpose**

|     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| **Category of personal information (data on fans)** | **Example** | **Purpose of use** |
| Contact details | Name, address, telephone number, email address | For administration purpose for providing the Services |
| Data related to operations carried out from our websites and applications | Products and tickets purchased, type of subscription, purchase history | Administrative, billing, marketing |
| Payment data and information related to the transaction made | Bank account number, credit card number | Administrative, billing and accounting |
| Reviews and comments on our websites and apps | Congratulations, comments, etc | Part of the Services, communication with other fans and friends |
| Data linked to the events | Arrival time, location, access door | Service optimization, marketing |
| Favorites | Country, team, player | Service quality, marketing |
